<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FRC 6390 DOCS on Athena Docs</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FRC 6390 DOCS on Athena Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:10:43 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VS Code</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/vscode/</guid>
      <description>What is VS Code? Visual Studio Code is an Integrated Development Environment or IDE, An IDE is often a program that programmers use to code and compile projects. Visual Studio Code is a versatile platform and can be used with almost any language. Along with being able to support many languages, it has a large community creating extensions which allow you to personalize, improve workflow, and add more support for even more languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:58:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/github/</guid>
      <description>What is GitHub? Github is a web-based platform with desktop support used for version control. Git simplifies the process of working with other people and makes it easy to collaborate on projects. Team members can work on files and easily merge their changes in with the master branch of the project.
Removes the need of using USB’s Makes communication easier Increases efficiency and productivity Free of Cost Creating an Account Visit https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WPILIB</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/wpilib/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:58:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/wpilib/</guid>
      <description>WPILib is the official resource library by FIRST, Worcester Polytechnic Institute and WPILib contributors. It is required to be able to compete in FIRST Robotic Competitions as it contains the required libraries to allow your robot to communicate and compete on the field. You can read the offical WPILib Documentation hereWhat is WPILib? WPILib is a library of pre-written code that allows you to control the hardware on your team&amp;rsquo;s robot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/java/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:58:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/java/</guid>
      <description>If this is your first time learning Java or are relatively unexperienced we recommend learning from W3Schools. Make sure you properly understand the basic syntaxand what methodsand conditionsare and how to make them.
Getting Java Installed We recommend installing java with the VS Code Java download, please make note of the Java version you are downloading. We will be using Java 17 but anything above 11 should work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAN Bus</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/can/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/can/</guid>
      <description>The CAN Bus is very important and you will most likely find yourself using it quite often as it provides amazing conveniences.
CAN or Controller Area Network is a standard design to allow devices and microcontrollers to communicate with each other. It uses a pair of wires, typically Green and Yellow. CAN can be configured in 3 ways.
Line Topology This is where each device connected links to the next device in the line with the end being terminated by a 120 ohm resisitor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motors</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/motors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/motors/</guid>
      <description>MOTORS In FRC it is important to know the hardware you will be working with, in this section we will cover popular motors you may encounter and how to tell the difference between them
When we talk about motors, we are talking more about motor controllers. Newer motors coming out may have this built in like the Falcon 500but many still require the speed controller.
CAN vs PWM Please read up on [CAN] if you are sure about any information portaining to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensors</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/sensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:59:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/sensors/</guid>
      <description>Some sensors have native support in WPI, but if you want to features offered by the vendor, you will need to install their custom vendor library.
Accelerometers Accelerometers measure acceleration (rate of change of velocity), an accelerometer typically uses 3 axes to measure acceleration but some may only measure in one direction. WPI has support for both types of single and tri-axis accelerometers. AnalogAccleromter, ADXL345_I2C, ADXL345_SP, ADXL362 and BuiltInAccelerometer for the Robrio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pneumatics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/pneumatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:59:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/pneumatics/</guid>
      <description>What Are Pneumatics And How Can They Be Used Pneumatics are a useful device that can be used to create simple actions, they work by expanding and retracting an arm in a cylinder in which works by using compressed air. In the image bellow you will see a pnuematic cylinder that is currently in the retreacted state. In most cases when it comes to FRC robots they are used for expanding and retracting intake subsystems, movinf arms, or even pulling or pushing a robot for end game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cameras</title>
      <link>http://example.org/introduction/cameras/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/introduction/cameras/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to competing in robot competitions it is is incredibly useful to have a secondary point of view for your robot which proves specifically useful when you are unable to see your robot in the field.
Point Of View Point of view is an important factor when it comes to competing, for instance if you were to have an intake system that needs to grab power cells or cargo as seen in the previous years it may seem as if you are positioned propperly to intake when you likely are not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alignment</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-drivetrain/swerve/alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:14:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-drivetrain/swerve/alignment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/driver-station/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:06:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/driver-station/introduction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera</title>
      <link>http://example.org/intro-to-frc-programming/camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/intro-to-frc-programming/camera/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limelight</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/limelight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/limelight/</guid>
      <description>Limelight is an incredibly useful vision processing tool in FRC which allows you to make accurate predictions and measurments based off a reflective tape on the FRC field, as well as by being used as a normal camera.
Downloading To get started we will need to install the latest Drivers, Image and Flasher from the Limelight Downloads PageDrivers After clicking the link to the Limelight downloads page you will be required to download the latest USB Driver and then run the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kauai Labs (NavX)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/kauai-labs-navx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:01:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/kauai-labs-navx/</guid>
      <description>Kauai Labs, one of the main IMU board providers, well known for there 9-axis inertial magnetic sensor and motion processor called the navX2-MXP.
Use Cases The navX2-MXP proccessor can help us obtain certain data, in which it can help us inhance our robot by giving us capabilities of programming specific features such as:
Field-Oriented Drive Auto-balance Auto-rotate to angle Motion Detection Collision Detection And much more Software Installation Inorder for us to use the navX devices we will be required to download the latest build version which can be found hereAfterwards it will be best to follow the steps on the Kauai Labs Website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REV Robotics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/rev/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/rev/</guid>
      <description>REV Robitcs is one of the main electronics provider in the FRC world as well as in other robotics competitions. Therefor REV has it own software interface that allows the configuration and for you to update the firmware of their own devices.
REV Hardware Client The REV hardware client allows you to edit the configuration of your REV devices by connecting to them manually via a USB Type C. This means we will be able to configure devices such as Spark Max motor controllers, the Control Hub and even the Expansion Board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross The Road Electronics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/ctre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/device-firmware/ctre/</guid>
      <description>Cross The Road Elctronics, also known as CTRE is one of the main FRC robot electronics provider while allowing for incredibly useful and neccesary tools for dignosing electronic devices and configurring them.
Pheonix Tools The Pheonix Library provided by CTRE is a great way to get started as they allow us to settup our devices once they are ready. The installation for the Pheonix Framework can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driver Station</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/driver-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/driver-station/</guid>
      <description>Driver Station is the program we use to control and communicate with our robot, it is required that Driver Station is connected and enabled before your robot will do anything. Your controller inputs and robot modes also go through Driver Station.
Driver Station Tour On the left, you will see 5 tabs. Each tab is important and has its own purpose, you will only need to worry about 3 for the majority of your time in Driver Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roborio</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/roborio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:59:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/roborio/</guid>
      <description>The Roborio is a powerful component on your robot
Your Roborio will need to be updated every season and sometimes with every WPI release, it is important to make sure the Roborio is up to date. Very often critical bugs and errors are found and fixed.
RIO 1 vs RIO 2 The roborio 1 and 2 are very similar, but the Rio 2 does provide some more features and contains better hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio</title>
      <link>http://example.org/robot-configuration/radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/robot-configuration/radio/</guid>
      <description>The Radio on your robot is how the information from your laptop gets to the robot wirelessly
Programming the Radio You will need to download the official radio configuration tool here, this page also includes all the steps you need to set up your radio for development
Getting Ready for Competition Your radio will work differently at a competition, it will need to be reprogrammed to connect to the FMS (Field Management System), there should be a station where you can bring your robot to reprogram the radio.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
